rankingham.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy | Rankingham.com

Last Updated: March 20, 2014

This page describes the methods of processing of personal data of users who use the platform Rankingham. This notice is provided pursuant to art. 13 of Legislative Decree. N. 196/2003 - Code regarding the protection of personal data. The information is provided only for the domain Rankingham.com and does not cover any other external web site may be accessed from the pages of Rankingham.

##  Finality 

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat your personal information on the site Rankingham. By accepting the Privacy Policy at the time of registration, you expressly consent to the use, storage and disclosure of your personal information. 

##  Collection 

You can access the site of Rankingham without revealing your identity or other personal information except for your email address. If you choose to provide this information, you consent to the collection and use of them as described on this page. If you decide to subscribe to the Advisory Agreement or Reception and Transmission Customer Orders and become so, you will be asked for more information, as required by law in order to able to provide you the service.  
**Rankingham may collect and store the following personal information:**

  * email address; 
  * name and other demographic information; 
  * answers to questions asked, relating in particular to your situation, experience and perception of financial issues; 
  * information from your interaction with our site, including statistics on the number of contacts, traffic to and from the site.  

##  Marketing 

Rankingham neither transfers nor cedes a fee your personal information to third parties for commercial purposes. Rankingham may use your contact and personal information to provide its products and services. If you do not wish to receive further communications from commercial Rankingham nor participate in our programs to customize our services, simply follow the instructions provided in communications or commercial messages received. 

##  Utilization 

Rankingham purpose in collecting your personal information for the following reasons: 

  * customize, measure and improve our future services, content and advertising; 
  * undergo any questionnaires in order to improve our services; 
  * inform you of our services, send commercial communications, updates and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; 
  * establish, in case you require it, the contractual relationship of the Service; 
  * to define a profile MiFID as required by law; 
  * to proceed to the correct identification according to Anti-money laundering legislation; 
  * comply with its obligations under these regulations; 
  * draw statistically and in an anonymous and aggregated data of all users in order to provide value-added services; 
  * work out the answers to the questionnaire and provide the results of the profiling process.   

##  Disclosure of your personal information 

Rankingham has the right to disclose personal information to respond to legal requests.   
Rankingham has the power to spread your personal information to the extent necessary to provide services. In no other case Rankingham may disclose and / or distribute your personal information without your consent.   
**Rankingham may share your personal information with:**

  * service providers with which Rankingham has a contractual relationship and collaborating with our business operations (such as affiliate programs, accounting and administrative management, mailing, payment or services of statistical analysis); 
  * banks affiliated with whom you yourself have chosen to establish a functional relationship to the services Rankingham; 
  * institutions against whom there are legal obligations;   

##  Cookies 

Rankingham uses "cookies" (wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) on certain pages of the site in order to analyze the access to web pages, customize their services, content and advertising, and ensure confidence and security. You can freely reject cookies, but in this case you may be prevented from using some features. Many of the used cookies are automatically deleted from the hard disk of the computer of the client at the end of each browsing session ("session cookies"). However, there are cookies that remain on your hard drive. Made a first visit to Rankingham, the system will be able to recognize in each subsequent visit that the customer has already been on this site ("cookie durable"). Thanks to this information could be presented or custom navigation paths. Please note that by default most web browsers are set to automatically accept cookies. Visitors / users can still change the default configuration. As stated above, disabling or deleting cookies, however, could prevent the optimal use of some areas of the site. If users / visitors want to decide each time whether to accept cookies, you can also configure your browser to generate a warning whenever a cookie is saved.  

##  Security 

Your data is stored on our servers in our hosting providers, on the territory of the European Community. Woman In some cases, a subset of your data may be stored on the servers of our service providers outside the territory of the European Union but still comply with the "Safe Harbor Privacy Principles".   
Rankingham treats data as an asset to be protected and uses a number of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information to access and activities of disclosure. However, you will be aware that third parties may unlawfully penetrate systems Rankingham, intercept, or illegally access transmissions or private communications, and other users may be used unlawfully or improperly disclose your personal information collected through the site. We work hard to protect your privacy, but we can not promise that your personal information will always remain private.   
& Nbsp; 

##  Third parties 

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from a Rankingham. If you disclose your personal information to others on other Internet sites, use and disclosure of the information you disclose may be subject to other rules. Rankingham does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. We invite you to take information about before communicating to others your personal information.   
& Nbsp; 

##  Miscellaneous 

Rankingham may at any time modify the content of this Privacy Policy by posting the new version of this page. All new terms and conditions will be effective from the date of publication. Rankingham will alert on its website and may, but is not required to, send an email to the address you provided. Please check this page periodically to check the current Privacy Policy. After each change, Rankingham consider your use of the platform as acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy.
